# MIGUEL RIQUELME

## FRONTEND ENGINEER · JS ENTHUSIAST

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm Miguel Riquelme, a Frontend developer since 2020, specializing in the JavaScript ecosystem. Seeking opportunities in the USA with a visa, aiming to collaborate and grow professionally. My daily tools include Next.js, React, JavaScript, TypeScript, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion, GraphQL, and REST API.

#### CONTACT

<u>+55 (11) 9 7797 - 6049</u>

miguelrisquelme@gmail.com

https://miguelito.dev

São Paulo, Brazil

#### EDUCATION

#### Impacta Tecnologia

Bachelor of Analysis Systems Development

Fev 2020 - Jul 2024

#### SKILLS

Skilled in Next.js, React, JavaScript,
TypeScript, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion,
GraphQL, and REST API. 2 years with
Next.js, 3 with React, 4 with JavaScript.
Strong in UI development, quick at
problem-solving. Intermediate level in
technical English, continuously improving.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Printi - uma empresa do grupo Cimpress

Mid-level Frontend Developer

Mai 2021 - Present (3 a)

Experienced Mid-level Frontend Developer skilled in React, JavaScript, and frontend tech. Proven track record in delivering high-quality solutions and driving innovation. Currently optimizing applications as a Front End React Developer at Printi.

### Etikett.de [Germany]

Frontend Developer

Dec 2022 - Ago 2023 (9 m)

Frontend Developer collaborating on company's new store development, creating pages, implementing features, and improving code robustness. Utilized Next.js, TypeScript, and WordPress CMS for seamless integration and enhanced user experiences.